{
    "question": "They are trained to give care to peple who are sick or injured. they work with doctors and others health care workers to make patients well and to keep them fit and healthy. they also help with end of life needs ans assist other famiy members with greiving.",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Nurse</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> Nurse they work with the doctors and caring for patients health</p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "bahasa-inggris-dari-jempol-adalah-a-mother-finger-b-little-fing-513",
            "question": "Bahasa Inggris dari jempol adalah.    A Mother Finger\r\nB. Little Finger\r\nC. Big Finger\r\nD. Large Finger\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><h3><strong>A. Mother finger</strong></h3><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>tapi </strong><strong>lebih</strong><strong> </strong><strong>tepatnya</strong><strong> </strong><strong>\"</strong><strong>THUMB</strong><strong>\"</strong><strong> </strong><strong>sih</strong></p><p> itu jawabannya sudah tepat</p><p></p><p><strong><em><u>JADIKAN JAWABAN TERBAIK JIKA ANDA MERASA TERBANTU\u2728</u></em></strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>jawabannya A. Mother Finger</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-jawaban-darifrom-of-the-following-statements-is-true-accordin-224",
            "question": "Apa jawaban darifrom of the following statements is true according to dhe to the advertisement above",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa jawaban dari pernyataan berikut ini yang benar menurut iklan di atas</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "13-they-not-attend-the-party-yesterday-a-do-c-doing-b-did-277",
            "question": "13. They ... not attend the party yesterday    a. Do\r\nc. Doing\r\nb. Did\r\nd. Does\r\n\r\n\r\nbantu jwab ya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>b. Did</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B.did</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>v2 karena  sudah terjadi</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "c-should-not-d-should-21-my-mom-says-i-play-more-with-my-958",
            "question": "C. Should not    D. Should\r\n21.\r\nMy mom says I..... play more with my pet when I am bored.\r\nA Has to\r\nB. Have to\r\nC. Must\r\nD. Should\r\nLast weekend I and my classmates went to the countryside to have a picnic. Befo\r\neaving, we made some sandwiches for lunch. We left quite early to avoid the trat\r\nam\r\nAfter driving for two hours, we arrived at a very nice place. It was near a river\r\nsome big trees around it. The driver parked the car under the tree. Seeing the e\r\nin cool water of the river, my friends and I decided to swim. After having\r\nmox the scenery We saw some beautiful\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>21. D (should)</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu^^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-the-setence-about-antumn-apa-artinya-267",
            "question": "Make the setence about antumn apa artinya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Buatlah kalimat tentang musim gugur.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Ralat tulisan yang autumn bukan antumn, terimakasih, selamat belajar</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-do-you-speak-these-named-asiti-breny-cbudi-883",
            "question": "How do you speak these named?\r\n a.SITI\r\n b.RENY\r\n c.BUDI",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>gh86fiyfihvyixgj8ycygij8</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "essays-1-give-2-examples-how-to-offering-help-2-what-is-narativ-333",
            "question": "Essays    1. Give 2 examples how to offering help\r\n2 What is \"Narative Text\r\n3. Write 2 sentences using \"should\r\n4. Name 2 examples of \"Quantifiers\"\r\n5 Give 1 sentence of \"Simple Past Tense\"\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Hello,how could i help you?</p><p>   Hey,may i help you with something?</p><p>2.  . . .</p><p>3.You should go to bed now,Nathan.</p><p>   i think you should get some rest</p><p>4. . . .</p><p>5 . . .</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "complete-the-sentences-use-the-present-continuous-from-of-the-the-417",
            "question": "Complete the sentences use the present continuous from of the the brackets    4. a. my uncle.....( wash ) his car. b.they ..... (listen) to the rock music\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>4. A. My uncle is washing his car. </p><p>B.  They are listening to the rock music. </p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu ^_^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p> </p><p>a.My uncle washed his car.</p><p>b.They listen to rock music.</p><p> </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "b-what-tara-must-do-before-go-to-riris-house-rearrange-these-s-221",
            "question": "B. What Tara must do before go to Riri's house?    Rearrange these sentences into a good paragraph!\r\n(1) Jack had an accident a few days ago\r\n(2) Jill went to the Hospital to visit him\r\n(3) He is still in the hospital now\r\n4) She is at hospital now\r\n5). He had to go to the hospital\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>halooo teks-nya mana ya? tolong tulis di komentar teksnya, biar saya jawab</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1-5-3-2-4</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>...........</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "siapa-saja-yang-termasuk-al-khulafa-u-ar-yasidin-sebutkan-650",
            "question": "Siapa saja yang termasuk al khulafa u ar yasidin sebutkan\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Abu Bakar Ash-Shiddiq,Umar bin Khattab,Utsman bin Affan,Ali bin Abi Thalib</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}